Nelly Goletti Papers
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 14. Professional Papers, 14; Boxes: 20 - 21 Folders: 341- 361
  - Programs - 1990 (Folder 352, Box 21)
  - Programs - 1995 (Folder 353, Box 21)
  - Programs - Undated (Folder 354, Box 21)
  - Programs: Les Ondes No. 65 7/26/42 (Folder 355, Box 21)
  - Records (Folder 356, Box 21)
  - Resume (Folder 357, Box 21)
  - Reviews (Folder 358, Box 21)
  - Script - "Maid Marion" (Folder 359, Box 21)
  - Script - The Nelly Goletti Show (Folder 360, Box 21)
  - Script - "Speak of the Devil.. ." (Folder 361, Box 21)
- 15. Personal Papers, 15; Box: 22 Folders: 362 – 371
  Series contains The Personal Papers series covers the life of Nelly Goletti and Frank Fusco outside of their professional lives. Most of the items in this series are official documents such as birth certificates, baptism papers, honorable discharge papers, identity cards, border crossing cards, marriage certificate, divorce papers, and cemetery deed. Along with these official papers, there are also telegraphs, letters, and a book that Nelly Goletti may have been reading. Items in this collection date from 1920 to 1994 but the bulk of items are from the 1950s.
  - Border Crossing Identification Book (Folder 362, Box 22)
  - Cemetery Deed - Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery (Folder 363, Box 22)
  - Divorce Certificate - Nelly Goletti and Louis Lafreyre (Folder 364, Box 22)
  - Frank Fusco Birth and Baptism Certificates (Folder 365, Box 22)
  - Frank Fusco Honorable Discharge Papers (Folder 366, Box 22)
  - French Identity Cards (Folder 367, Box 22)
  - Marriage Book (French) - Nelly Goletti and Frank Fusco (Folder 368, Box 22)
  - Marriage Certificates - Nelly Goletti and Frank Fusco (Folder 369, Box 22)
  - Misc. (Folder 370, Box 22)
  - Misc. (Folder 371, Box 22)
- 16. Handwritten Songs by Other Composers, 16; Box: 23 Folders: 372 - 373
  - Nom me lo Sichi - Guiseppy Chiri (Folder 372, Box 23)
  - Les Enfants - Masseneh (Folder 373, Box 23)
- 17. Practice Books, 17; Boxes: 23 - 32 Folders: 374 - 412
  - Abadie - Audran (Folder 374, Box 23)
  - Arienzo (Folder 375, Box 23)
  - Bach (Folder 376, Box 23)
  - Bach (Folder 377, Box 23)
  - Bach (Folder 378, Box 24)
  - Beaune - Beethoven (Folder 379, Box 24)
  - Beethoven (Folder 380, Box 24)
  - Beethoven (Folder 381, Box 25)
  - Beethoven Part II (Folder 382, Box 25)
  - Bendel -Brahms (Folder 383, Box 25)
  - Bizet (Folder 384, Box 25)
  - Blaquiere (Folder 385, Box 25)
  - Bretonne (Folder 386, Box 25)
  - Brooks - Chausson (Folder 387, Box 26)
  - Burgmein (Folder 388, Box 26)
  - Cayrou (Folder 389, Box 26)
  - Chopin (Folder 390, Box 26)
  - Chopin (Folder 391, Box 26)
  - Chopin (Folder 392, Box 27)
  - Chopin (Folder 393, Box 27)
  - Chopin (Folder 394, Box 27)
  - Chopin - Clementi (Folder 395, Box 28)
  - Clementi - Czemy (Folder 396, Box 28)
  - Czemy - Falla (Folder 397, Box 28)
  - Faucher - Gyorgy (Folder 398, Box 29)
  - Gerard (Folder 399, Box 29)
  - Gounod (Folder 400, Box 29)
  - Halvey - Liszt (Folder 401, Box 29)
  - Lacome (Folder 402, Box 30)
  - Liszt (Folder 403, Box 30)
  - Liszt - Moscheles (Folder 404, Box 30)
  - Mascagni (Folder 405, Box 30)
  - Mozart - Nieman (Folder 406, Box 31)
  - Novaro - Raff (Folder 407, Box 31)
  - Rameau (Folder 408, Box 31)
  - Ravel - Schumann (Folder 409, Box 31)
  - Rossini (Folder 410, Box 32)
  - Sinding - Weckerlin (Folder 411, Box 32)
  - Misc. (Folder 412, Box 32)
- 18. Audio Collection, 18; Boxes: 33 - 34 Folders: 413 - 414
  Series contains 4 records and 3 cassettes of Nelly Golleti’s “Pianiste Extraordinaire" recording which was released in 1982.
  Alphabetical by Title
  - Pianiste Extraordinaire (4 Records) (Folder 413, Box 33)
  - Pianiste Extraordinaire (3 cassette tapes) (Folder 414, Box 34)
- 19. Audio – Original Form, 19; Box: 34 Folders: 415 - 417
  Series contains personal recordings of performances by Nelly Goletti. There is no indication whether or not the recordings were later released to the public.
  - Program A and B (Folder 415, Box 34)
  - "Nelly Live at the Bardavon" 09/23/94 (Folder 416, Box 34)
  - "An Evening in Paris" (Folder 417, Box 34)
- 20. Cassettes, 20; Box: 34 Folders: 418 – 419
  - Program One and Two (2 Cassettes) (Folder 418, Box 34)
  - Nelly Colette 94 and 95 (2 Cassettes) (Folder 419, Box 34)